http://www.efilmcritic.com/hbs.cgi?privacy

More in-depth film festival coverage than any other website!
HBS Entertainment Networks Statement of Privacy
Since we were founded, HBS Entertainment Networks has tried to help its users
retain their privacy while they take advantage of all the Internet has to
offer. We are committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology
that gives you the safest and most powerful online experience that you can get
anywhere. And beer. If you have questions about this, please write us
at .
Privacy Principles
Because your privacy is important to us, we will operate by the following five principles.
Principle 1
HBS Entertainment Networks (incorporating eFilmCritic.com and HollywoodBitchslap.com) explicitly asks when it needs information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") beyond your name and email address. HBS Entertainment Networks asks for general contact information only occasionally and, where appropriate, credit card information through third party sellers. No credit card information is stored on our server at any time.
Principle 2
HBS Entertainment Networks and our affiliates and service partners use limited Personal Information to operate the HBS Entertainment Networks sites and services, to communicate with you regarding your account and to compile general demographic statistics.
Principle 3
HBS Entertainment Networks will never disclose your Personal Information unless required to do so by order of a court of law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on HBS Entertainment Networks, or our sites; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of HBS Entertainment Networks, our sites or the users of said sites; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of HBS Entertainment Networks, our sites or the public.
Principle 4
As part of your participation in any of HBS Entertainment Networks' services, we allow you to elect to receive or not receive certain information and e-mail from our websites or their service partners. From time to time, HBS Entertainment Networks may be required to send you information about the service or your account. Except as mentioned above, HBS Entertainment Networks will never send you unsolicited information, commercial offers or advertisements, including e-mail.
Principle 5
If at any time you believe that HBS Entertainment Networks has not adhered to
these principles, please notify us by e-mail at
and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.
What about cookies?
To make it easy and convenient for you to login to our services, the HBS Entertainment Networks sites do require you to enable cookies to utilize all of our services. Because we use cookies, you can bookmark your Hollywood Bitchslap or eFilmCritic start page and access your account without logging in. No private information is garnered via cookies use.
Does HBS Entertainment Networks share my Personal Information with other companies?
We never share your Personal Information, except with partners who assist in providing services or products associated with our sites, and only after you have expressed interest in receiving such offers. Other companies may have access to your Personal Information to provide routine services, such as credit card processing for items purchased, or may provide other essential elements of the site.
Third Party Advertising
We use Ugo and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser(s) may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
eFilmCritic.com: Australia's Largest Movie Review Database.Privacy Policy | HBS Inc. |
|   All data and site design copyright 1997-2017, HBS Entertainment, Inc.
